Viewers all over the world, whatever you are using to view us,
ask the evil spirit to leave your life, in the name of Jesus!
Leave my life!
You evil spirit, leave my life!
Open your lips - ask the evil spirit to leave your life, to leave your career.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
That spirit of nightmare, limitation, stagnation, affliction, leave my life!
Prayer!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers all over the world, wherever that disease, affliction - leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
I command you, you affliction, leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
Leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
Where can you go from His presence?
When Jesus says, "Out! You affliction, out! You sickness, out!", who can say, "No"?
I say to you affliction, in the name of Jesus, out!
In my blood - out! In my bones - out! In my kidneys - out! In my liver - out!
Wherever it is located, in the name of Jesus, you affliction,
wherever it is located in my bones, blood, liver, kidneys, organ - out, in the name of Jesus!
TT: Unknown
RV: Mel Flowers 16/11/2018